麦琪:谁说中国菜吃不饱肚子的?
Maggie: Who says Chinese food can't be filling?
杰森:本.
Jason: Ben.
本:把像鼻涕一样的东西给我.
Ben: Pass the food that looks like snot.
杰森:喔,本!
Jason: Aw, Ben!
迈克:好,好,
Mike: Now, now, let's not get tense with the little lad.
就让他多吃一点吧,这很可能是Ben的最后的一顿饭了.
I mean, after all, this could be Ben's last meal.
本:嘿,我明天要做大手术,
Ben: Hey, I don't need to hear stuff like that when I got major surgery
你别来讲这种倒霉的话.
tomorrow.
开萝尔:本你那是小手术.
Carol: Ben, minor surgery.
本:留着割你脖子时说吧.
Ben: Say that when they're going to cut your throat.
麦琪:本我的小南瓜,割扁桃是十分简单的事,
Maggie: Ben, having your tonsils out is a simple thing.
你根本不用担心,这就像玩一样.
It's nothing to worry about. It's probably fun!
杰森:亲爱的.
Jason: Honey.
麦琪:我讲过头了.
Maggie: I went to far?
杰森:是的.
Jason: Yes.
麦琪:注意,开始了,
Maggie: Ok, everybody fortune cookies and I'll go first.
幸运之饼我第一个拿.哦,你的家将永远充满无限的欢乐和笑声.
Your home will always be filled with the sounds of laughter.
本:对不起.
Ben: Excuse me.
杰森:看我的,当您享用了洲式中式中国点心以后,请你再尝尝洲式墨西哥点心, 点心用料讲究,制作精细,包您吃了赞不绝口.
Jason: Close. Alright. If you enjoy Chou's take out Chinese Kitchen, be sure to try
Chou's Mexican kitchen. 110 South of the Border on trays served in that
very oriental stylish
flair. Now back to your meal
本:爸爸你那是广告.
Ben: Dad! You got a commercial!
麦琪:该你了迈克.
Maggie: You're up, Mike.
迈克:好的,好的,迈克·西维尔会有什么好运?出名,发财.
Mike: Ok, ok. What will Mike Seaver's fortune be? Fame? Fortune?
开萝尔:桃花运?
Carol: Clear skin?
杰森:开萝尔!
Jason: Carol.
迈克:风水轮流转,开萝尔抱歉,该是你的.
Mike: Every dog has his day. Eh, sorry, Carol. I got yours.
开萝尔:那么这个该是你的,一位英俊绅士将向你求婚.
Carol: So, this must be yours. A handsome gentleman will ask for your hand.
麦琪:你们俩都给我停下.
Maggie: Kids cut it out!
杰森:好本,该你了.
Jason: Alright, Ben, your fortune.
本:爸爸我打开前,你先说什么是小手术.
Ben: Ok. But before I open this, what makes this minor surgery?
杰森:好吧,你是病人,
Jason: Well, you're the patient and you're a minor. So, it's minor surgery.
你是小孩,所以就是小手术.
Ok, I'm joking, Ben. I'm joking.
好,跟你开玩笑本,我能和你开玩笑,
The reason I can joke is because there's really nothing that can go wrong.
就充分说明这手术没什么好担心的,现在我以一个父亲和一位医生的身份告诉你,
I'm telling you as your father and as doctor that a tonsillectomy is about
摘除扁桃体,是一种最简单的手术.
the easiest kind of surgery there is.
麦琪:我们俩整天在医院里陪着你.亲爱的.
Maggie: And we'll be with you at the hospital all day, sweetheart.
本:可我喜欢扁桃体,我舍不得离开它们.
Ben: But I like my tonsils. I'm attached to them.
迈克:就要离了.对了,
Mike: Not for long. Oh, um, yea right.
我跟波纳约好一起温习功课的.
Well, I got to go study for that test with Boner.
本:迈克你讲好跟我一起玩电子游戏的.
Ben: But, Mike, you said you'd play some video games with me.
迈克:我倒是很想跟你玩,不过功课要紧.
Mike: Oh, I'd love to, Benny, but, uh, schoolwork comes first.
本:开萝尔一起玩超人维特兄弟.
Ben: Carol? A little Super Veto Brothers?
开萝尔:抱歉本,我有功课要复习了.
Carol: Sorry, Ben. I've got homework that I'm actually going to do.
杰森:本我来跟你玩那个超人维特.
Jason: Well, Ben, I'll take some of that Super Veto action.
本:爸爸你水平不够.
Ben: But, Dad, you stink.
麦琪:本!
Maggie: Ben!
本:那怎么说,这是事实.
Ben: What can I say? It's true.
杰森:没关系.
Jason: Ok.
本:这可能是我最后玩一次电子游戏.
Ben: It's just that it may be the final game I ever play.
开萝尔:本,行了,
Carol: Ben enough. This is not the final game of any kind.
这绝不是你最后一次,你明天晚上回家跟现在一样好,也许更好.
You'll be back here tomorrow night as good as new. Maybe better.
本:但愿这样.
Ben: Yea, right.
杰森:打开你的幸运之饼,要收拾桌子了.
Jason: Come on, open that fortune cookie so we can finish clearing.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
本:是空白的.
Ben: It's blank.
杰森:这就是静脉输液管,医生就是用它把营养液输进你的身体里去的.
Jason: This is the intravenous tubes that the doctor's use to feed healthy fluids directly into your body.
本:我宁可用自己的嘴巴来吃营养.
Ben: I'd rather feed myself the old-fashioned way.
麦琪:本你放心吧,
Maggie: Just remember, sweetheart,
医生和护士全都会对你很好的.
that the doctors and nurses are here to help you.
本:我昨晚吃的是中国菜.
Ben: I had Chinese food last night.
护士:明天我家里也吃.
Nurse: I'll tell my family.
杰森:他们现在要把你送到手术室里去,
Jason: So, next thing, Ben,
然后就开始给你上麻药,
they'll take you into the operation room then they give you the anesthesia
上了麻药以后你就什么也不知道了.
that'll put you to sleep just like that. You won't feel a thing.
本:难道我非开刀不可吗?
Ben: Do we have to do this?
麦琪:宝贝,你的扁桃体经常发炎,一定得割掉.
Maggie: Come on, honey. Your tonsils keep getting infected. They have to go.
本:可是我害怕.
Ben: But I'm scared.
麦琪:我知道宝贝.
Maggie: Oh, I know, sweetheart. I know.
本:你会好的,我保证.
Ben: You'll be fine, I promise.
玛奎兹医生:没问题.嗨Maggie.
Dr. Marquez: He sure will! Hi, Maggie.
Jason: Oh, Hi Jerry. Ben, say good morning to Dr. Marquez
本:算了吧.
Ben: Forget it.
Dr. Marquez: Benjamin. Don't tell me you're afraid of a little snip snip
没事.
I see.
杰森:是啊,Jerry,他还是相当紧张的.
Jason: Yes, well, Jerry, he's a little nervous.
护士:你想跑到哪去伙计?
Nurse: Where do you think you're going, buddy?
本:我想上厕所,我不叫什么伙计.
Ben: I was going to the bathroom. And my name's not buddy.
护士:现在已经太晚了,不过你要真想小便,给,专给病人的.
Nurse: Well, that's too late. But if you have to go, here, the motorman's friend.
本:不要了.
Ben: I'll wait.
Dr. Marquez: So, Benjamin, what do you say? Are we ready
杰森:别怕,本勇敢些.姓西维尔的都是好样的.
Jason: Oh, come on, Ben. Buck up. Show them what you're made of. Be a Seaver.
本:我姓西维尔,扁桃也姓西维尔的.
Ben: I am a Seaver and so are my tonsils.
杰森:本·西维尔就该迎着困难上,西维尔什么都不怕,
Jason: Well, Seavers face their problems head on.
什么都挡不住他们.
They don't run away from things and they don't let their fears get in the way.
本:所有姓西维尔的?
Ben: All of the Seavers?
杰森:当然.
Jason: You bet!
本:那我就不愿意姓西维尔了.
Ben: Then I don't want to be a Seaver.
杰森:本.
Jason: Oh, Ben.
本:是真的,我不姓西维尔了,可以回家了吗?
Ben: I mean it. I'm not a Seaver. Can I go home now?
护士:得进去了.
Nurse: Here we go.
本:我不想做手术!!
Ben: I don't want to go like this!
麦琪:别担心!本,我们都爱你!
Maggie: Don't worry, Ben! We love you!
玛奎兹医生:本杰明?你现在是否还有知觉玛?
Dr. Marquez: Benjamin? Can you feel the anesthesia yet?
本:什么也没感到.
Ben: I don't feel anything.
护士:一切正常.
Nurse: Good sign.
玛奎兹医生:现在你听我说,你要是把你爱看的电视片一部一部的念出来,你很快就会睡着的,比如Kildad博士,医学中心,约翰杀人狂.
Dr. Marquez: You know, sometimes, I find patients your age relax and go to sleep a little quicker if they do something like naming their favorite TV shows, you know, like Dr. Kildad, Medical Center, Tropa John, M.D.?
本:恩?
Ben: Huh?
玛奎兹医生:还有变形金刚,你爱看什么片子?
Dr. Marquez: You know, the Gonza? What do you like to watch?
本:皮维剧场,激烈跟宝岛,
Ben: Pee Wee's Playhouse, Gilligan's Island, other stuff like Who's the Boss?
还有什么谁是头,以及突击队,
Moonlighting and the one that comes in between them,
还有这两部中间的那部,你知道我指什么?
you know which one I mean.
玛奎兹医生:不,我不知道.
Dr. Marquez: No, I don't.
本:你没看真可惜,里面的那个男孩真可怜.
Ben: Oh, you should see it sometime. The little kid on it's really good.
本:多难为情.
Ben: How embarrassing.
出租车司机:想出去吗伙计?
Skipper: Whoa! Going somewhere, little buddy?
本:你们怎么搞的,我不叫伙计,我叫本.
Ben: What's with you people? My name's not buddy, it's Ben!
出租车司机:你想去哪?本!
Skipper: Ok, going somewhere, Ben?
本:好吧,想出去吗Ben?
Ben: Yea, hey, can you give me a ride?
出租车司机:对,你能送我去吗?看见这个字了吗?我戴这种帽子,不开出租车,那会是干什么呢?现在走?
Skipper: You see this sign on my cap? I couldn't walk around with this sign on my cap if that wasn't what I do. Are you ready?
本:这就走.真讨厌.
Ben: I'm ready! How embarrassing.
出租车司机:要去哪儿小孩?
Skipper: Where to, Benny boy?
本:你送我离开那医院,越远越好,
Ben: As far away from this hospital place as I can!
你知道他们拿我怎么样?一定要割我的脖子.
You know what they were going to do to me? Cut my tonsils out!
出租车司机:是因为你的扁桃体发炎,对吗?
Skipper: Oh, just because they kept getting infected, right?
本:你也懂?
Ben: You know it.
出租车司机:他们准是给你上麻药,
Skipper: And I bet they told you they were going to put you to sleep but
等你睡着后再开刀.
you wouldn't feel a thing.
本:是的.
Ben: Yup!
出租车司机:你信他们吗?
Skipper: Did you believe them?
本:你看我像不像傻瓜.
Ben: What do I look like, a dope?
出租车司机:你穿的那玩意儿,是有点像傻瓜样.
Skipper: Well, you do look pretty silly in that getup.
本:知道,是他们逼我穿的.
Ben: Yea, I know they made me wear it.
出租车司机:我先送你回去,罗宾汉路15号,
Skipper: Look, why don't we take you home, 15 Robin Hood Lane,
让你换一换衣服,然后再决定去什么地方?
and get you some real clothes? Then you can decide where we go next!
本:好主意,请你找到罗宾汉路15号.
Ben: Great idea! Take me home! 15 Robin Hood Lane.
出租车司机:这个我知道.
Skipper: I just said that.
本:你怎么会知道的?
Ben: But how'd you know that?
出租车司机:我不是早就说过了吗,我是个出租司机小伙计.
Skipper: Like I told you before, that's what I'm here for, little buddy.
本:哦,是吗?我说你很像加利刚宝岛里的那个船长.
Ben: Ok. You know, you look just like the Skipper on Gilligan's island!
出租车司机:哦,我不知道,像这种电视我是不大看的.
Skipper: Oh, I wouldn't know. I don't watch TV much myself.
本:伙计,你车座位太旧了.
Ben: Boy, you know, your seats are really old.
本:还带什么?这有恐龙大战,红色小马,死一样寂静,这就够了.
Ben: Ok, now, we got Dinosaur Heads, Phony Baloney, Silent But Deadly That should do it.
出租车司机:别忘了本,得带上你的衬衣衬裤.
Skipper: Don't forget, Ben! You're going to need some underwear!
本:对,谢谢.
Ben: Thanks!
出租车司机:我就是让你来拿衣服的.
Skipper: That's what I'm here for!
本:多带一条保险.
Ben: Better safe than sorry.
迈克:了不起,想不到本还那么勇敢.
Mike: Boy, am I impressed. I didn't think he'd go through with it!
本:糟了.
Ben: Yikes.
开萝尔:哦,我真为他而感到自豪.
Carol: Oh! I'm so glad we're related!
迈克:是这样的.
Mike: Oh, you said it!
麦琪:咱们的小天使他来了.
Maggie: Here comes my little angel!
杰森:我们的班尼.
Jason: Here's Benny!
本:这小子是谁?
Ben: Who is this weeny?
本的替身:回到家真是高兴,是啊,
New Ben: Sure is great to be home.
看到全家人这样幸福的在一起,使我感到真激动.
Gosh, seeing my whole family together like this just makes me feel so swell!
本:激动?
Ben: Swell?
本的替身:我看开刀并没什么了不起.爸爸妈妈是不该怕,
New Ben: Boy, that operation was a snap! Mom, Dad, you were right.
我当时的胆子的确太小了.
I was so silly to be that scared. Now, gee wilickers!
像我现在这样,我是精神百倍.
I feel like a new man!
本:究竟是怎么回事?这小子到底是什么人?妈妈你干嘛要喊他Ben.
Ben: What's going on here? How do you guys know this gopher? Mom! Why are you calling him Ben?
麦琪:我们为什么要这样干坐着呢?
Maggie: Well, what are we sitting here for?
你要吃一点冰激凌吗Ben?
What do you say to some ice cream, Ben?
本:热烈拥护冰激凌.
Ben: I say, Hello ice cream!
本的替身:妈妈你真要我吃吗?
New Ben: You really think I should Mom?
吃了冰激凌就吃不下晚饭了.
I mean, I don't want to spoil my dinner.
杰森:算了吧,没关系.
Jason: Aw, come on. It's ok.
本:你们并不是跟我讲话,是吗?
Ben: You weren't talking to me at all, were you?
麦琪:我的小南瓜,你刚割了扁桃体,吃吧.
Maggie: Pumpkin, you just had your tonsils out!
本的替身:但是...
New Ben: But…
麦琪:为了我?
Maggie: For me?
本的替身:那好吧,我只吃一勺.
New Ben: Shucks, maybe half a scoop.
本:迈克,妈妈 ,开萝尔,爸爸,
Ben: Mike! Mom! Carol! Dad! Whoa.
哇!好吧,你们谁都不理我,从此以后我也不理你们.
Well, I'm not talking to any of you either since you just walked through me.
本的替身:既然让我吃,那我就吃了.
New Ben: Mm-mm. Sure glad you talked me into this, Ma.
杰森:你们俩听着,你们的弟弟今天在医院里的勇敢表现,
Jason: Kids, your brother's bravery at the hospital this morning was frankly
是很了不起的.
the stuff of legends.
麦琪:你真的不想再填一点冰激凌了Ben?
Maggie: Are you sure you don't want any more ice cream, Ben?
本的替身:不,谢谢妈妈,我得注意体重.
New Ben: No, thanks, Mom. Gotta watch my weight.
本:天呐,把那小子当成我了.
Ben: Boy, how come they think this guy is me?
麦琪:好.
Maggie: Ok, then.
本:哦,他把冰激凌全拿走了,
Ben: Oh, sure. Put the ice cream away.
看不见我,也听不见我,什么也不给我吃.
You can't hear me, you can't see me, why feed me?
本的替身:妈妈爸爸我能离开一下吗?
New Ben: Mom, Dad, may I be excused?
我想在晚饭前把屋子打扫一下.
I'd like to do some cleaning up around the house before dinner.
杰森:可以,乖孩子,真乖.
Jason: Of course, son of mine.
本:注意体重先生,你就要倒霉了.
Ben: Oh, now you're gonan get it Mr. Watching my weight.
迈克:你快给我放下,哦,我这件可是高级皮夹克,我说过谁也不许碰它,特别是你记得吗?
Mike: Whoa, whoa, Benski. Now look, this is the leather jacket of mine that no
one is allowed to touch especially you, remember
本:揍他,迈克揍他.
Ben: Hit him, Mike, hit him!
迈克:不过我重新考虑过了,现在我已经不想要它了,
Mike: But, uh, you know, I've been thinking and well,
我把它送给你穿你要吗?
I don't want it anymore. Heck, why don't you just keep the darn thing?
本:什么?
Ben: What?
本的替身:什么,真的送给我.
New Ben: You really mean it, Mike?
迈克:当然了.
Mike: I sure do!
本:我都要吐了.
Ben: I'm gonna puke.
迈克:我穿你这件旧的行吗?好吧,我有事要走了,回见.
Mike: I'll just wear your old one, ok? Ok, I'll see you guys later!
本的替身:回见迈克,祝你快乐.
New Ben: See ya, Mike! Have a neat-o time!
迈克:很谢谢弟弟.哦,
Mike: Hey, thanks bro. Holy Moly! What was I thinking?
我的天呐,我这人怎么了,
Now, how could I just leave this house when I can stick around here and
我既然会把本放在家里,我干嘛不跟他玩反而要出去呢?
play with good ol' Ben?
本:我知道我吐不出.
Ben: I knew it. Nothin'.
开萝尔:不迈克,你走,我来陪你玩怎么样?玩超人Veto兄弟好吗?
Carol: No, Mike, you go. I'll stay and play with little Ben. Hey, Ben, how about a little Super Veto brothers?
迈克:不不不开萝尔,我要跟本玩.
Mike: No, no, no wait Carol. I'm playing with Ben.
开萝尔:不,我要陪他
Carol: No, I am.
迈克:我要陪他玩.
Mike: But, I want to.
开萝尔:我要
Carol: Well so do I
迈克:是我先讲好的.
Mike: Yea. Well, I said it first.
开萝尔:你不要脸.
Carol: Well, big wow.
迈克:你才不要脸呢.
Mike: Well, double big wow.
麦琪:哦波纳,开萝尔跟迈克又在斗了.
Maggie: Jason! Carol and Mike are fighting again!
杰森:我知道,你准备拿他们怎么样?
Jason: Oh, no. What are we going to do?
本的替身:开萝尔,迈克我们三个人一起玩,不是更好吗?
New Ben: Mike. Carol. Why don't the three of us play a game together?
杰森:不是你提醒我不知该怎么好了.
Jason: I don't know what we'd do without you.
麦琪:哦,简直无法想象.
Maggie: Oh, I can't imagine.
本的替身:嗨,我有个更好的主意,我们全家一起玩电子游戏好不好?我们不玩那些新出来的,爸爸不会玩的电子游戏.
New Ben: Hey, I've got an even better idea! Why doesn't the whole family play something together? And not one of those new fangled video games that Dad has so much trouble with.
杰森:还说什么我水平不够?水平不够.
Jason: What can I say? I stink.
本的替身:我们玩全家福好吗?
New Ben: Let's play a board game!
家人:好.
Everybody: Yes!
杰森:本你也太聪明了.
Jason: Ben, you're the greatest!
本:我要吐的出,就吐在他脸上.
Ben: If I could puke right now, I'd puke on him.
迈克:嗨,还等着干什么?
Mike: Hey, what're we waiting for?
本的替身:嗨,你们先把桌子摆好,
New Ben: Hey, you guys go set up the card table.
我到房间里把游戏机拿出来.
I'll get a game from my room and be right down!
麦琪:我们等着你亲爱的.
Maggie: We'll miss you sweetheart.
本:怎么了,你们认错人了,他不是本,我才是本.
Ben: Wait, can't you guys see? That's not Ben! I'm Ben!
本的替身:你才不是呢小子.
New Ben: Not anymore, Sport!
本:好吧,好吧,
Ben: That's it! That's it!
我这就上去跟这小子好好的算账.
That phony pants and I are gonna settle this right now!
本:我问你小混蛋,你来这干嘛?
Ben: Alright weeny head. What do you think you're doing?
本的替身:我要跟全家一起玩游戏.
New Ben: I'm about to play a game with my family.
本:别来这套,你知道你在跟谁讲话?
Ben: Don't give me that. Remember who you're talking to.
本的替身:跟个小子讲话.
New Ben: I'm talking to nobody.
本:你在跟本·西维尔讲话.
Ben: You're talking to Ben Seaver.
本的替身:不,你在跟Ben Seaver讲话.
New Ben: No, you're talking to Ben Seaver.
本:嗨,你能骗得了他们,可你骗不了我,你绝不是我,你也不知道我把东西放在哪儿.
Ben: Hey just because you got dimples, doesn't mean anything. I know you're not me. I mean, you don't know stuff like where I keep my
本的替身:是护身符,好吧,
New Ben: Good luck charms?
洗过裤子,被我藏在皮靴里就不会让妈妈扔掉了.
Well, the lucky pants are rolled up in my left logger boots so Mom won't
那银元放在火柴盒里,
throw them out and the silver dollar's in a matchbox right behind the
埋在车库排水管后面,还有那只乌龟壳子藏在.
garage drain pipe, right next to the magazines.
本:天呐.
Ben: Gah.
本的替身:别坐在我床上.
New Ben: Please don't sit on my bed.
本:我一定要揍你.
Ben: I'm gonna slug you!
本的替身:嗨,你别这样,这可不是我的错.
New Ben: Hey, take it easy! All this isn't my fault.
本:不是你的错?
Ben: No?
本的替身:对,是你的错,你说过你不愿意姓西维尔的.
New Ben: No. It's yours! You're the one who said you didn't want to be a Seaver!
本:我可从来没讲过这种蠢话.
Ben: I'd never say anything stupid like that!
本的替身:在医院的走廊里,就在你进手术室以前,
New Ben: In the hospital hall,
记得吗?
right before the operation you chickened out of, remember?
本:那我就不愿意姓西维尔.
Ben: Then I don't want to be a Seaver.
本:我确实是说过这种蠢话.
Ben: I did say something stupid like that.
本的替身:所以你就让了位,这一点我得感谢你,
New Ben: So, I got the job.
这是好差事.
I guess I should thank you, it was a good deal.
本:不过我是说着玩的,我很愿意姓Seaver.
Ben: But, I didn't mean it. I want to be a Seaver.
本的替身:太晚了,你看.抱歉伙计.
New Ben: Too late, see? Sorry, buddy.
本:我不是伙计,我是……这下完了.
Ben: My name's not buddy, it's Nobody.
本的替身:你看看这张全家福吧.你尽管喊叫吧,
New Ben: If you like that, you're gonna love this.
再想也没用.
Scream all you want to, it's not going to help.
本:那好吧,反正我说不清了.
Ben: You're right. I'm done talking.
本的替身:你这样干可没好处,我看你算了.
New Ben: I wouldn't do that if I were you. And I am.
本:怎么回事,我刚才在楼上现在在楼下,
Ben: What gives here? First I was upstairs, now I'm downstairs.
刚才是白天现在是晚上.
It was day, now it's night?
麦琪:谁说中国菜吃不饱肚子的.
Maggie: Who says Chinese food can't be filling?
迈克:本.
Mike: Ben.
本的替身:这个鸭子汁太棒了.
New Ben: This duck sauce is divine.
迈克:这可是本手术以后吃的第一顿饭.
Mike: Wow, you know. This is going to be Benny's first tonsil free meal!
本的替身:那只是个小手术迈克,我是小孩,只做小手术,懂吗?
New Ben: It was only minor surgery, Mike. I'm a minor, it was surgery, get it?
杰森:本你说的太好了.
Jason: That's a good one, Ben.
本:你也会说这话.爸爸.
Ben: You would say that, Dad.
麦琪:好了,大家注意,幸运之饼现在开始,看你的运气本.
Maggie: Ok, everybody. Fortune cookies and you go first, Ben.
本的替身:那好吧.
New Ben: Okey dokey.
本:你什么也没有,那是空白的
Ben: You're wasting your time. It's blank.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
本的替身:你将永远和幸福的家庭在一起.
New Ben: You will have a long life with your loving family.
本:这是不可能的事,我准是在做梦.
Ben: This can't be happening. I must be dreaming.
迈克:妈妈爸爸我建议我们干一杯,为本,我亲爱的小弟弟.
Mike: Mom, Dad. I'd like to propose a toast. To Ben, the bestest little brother…
杰森:为儿子.
Jason: Or son!
迈克:哦,对不起,和儿子,我们全家的宝贝,为Ben.
Mike: Or excuse me, a son, a family could ever have!
家人:为本干杯!
Everyone: To Ben!
本:我今天要是知道会有这样的结果,我还不如去挨它一刀呢,
Ben: Oh, I would've had that dumb old operations if I would've known I
我就不应该逃出医院,
wouldn't be a Seaver anymore. I should've never left the hospital.
怎么回事?他害怕了.
What is it? I said something.
迈克:班尼没事吧,你脸色好白.
Mike: Hey, Benny, you ok? You look kinda pale.
本:要扭转过来,我看还不算晚.
Ben: I can turn this around! It's not too late!
本的替身:我去取点牛奶,
New Ben: I'm gonna go get some milk!
喝点牛奶对我有好处.
It's good for me and it tastes good, too.
本:我要是马上回医院,事情肯定能扭转过来.
Ben: If I go back to the hospital, I can get my life back, can't I?
本的替身:不,不可能的.
New Ben: No! No, you can't!
本:能,我能,我能,我能.
Ben: Yea, I can, I can, that's it!
本的替身:不可能的本.
New Ben: No, it won't work, Ben. I mean
本:你喊我了.
Ben: You said it. You're not Ben, I'm Ben!
杰森:你不是本我是本.
Jason: What was that?
麦琪:是谁?不知道,我也听见了,像是孩子.
Maggie: I don't know. I heard it, too. Sounded like a kid.
杰森:是啊.我们爱的孩子.
Jason: Yea. A kid we know and love.
本:快,快,快送我回医院去.
Ben: Ha! Quick! Quick! Quick! Back to the hospital!
出租车司机:哦,这可不行,我只开单程车,这是公司的规定.
Skipper: Oh, no can do. I only take one way rides. Company policy.
本:你得送我,送我去,送我去.
Ben: But you got to! You got to! You got to!
出租车司机:不,我不去,我不去,我不去.
Skipper: No, I don't! I don't! I don't!
本:你听我说,我要把我的生活找回来.
Ben: But you don't understand. I gotta get my life back.
出租车司机:我要是让你找回生活,
Skipper: Well, if I let you get your life back,
那就会让别人失去好生活的.
then I gotta let everybody get their lives back.
本:可是我……
Ben: But I wanna…
出租车司机:不过你要是想到别的地方去,那我倒是可以的,
Skipper: If you can figure out a new place to go, then I'm your man.
短程的或者远程的,三个小时的也可以.你小子干什么?
Short trip, long trip. Heck, three hour tour! What are you doing?
本:不知道.太好了我能开车了.
Ben: I don't know! Holy Cow! I can drive!
本:嘿,这有人吗?我不喜欢这个地方.
Ben: Hey! Is anybody here? I don't like the looks of this. Neither do I.
我也不喜欢.玛奎兹医生,我回来了.
Dr. Marquez! I'm back.
玛奎兹医生:护士,今天到此为止.
Dr. Marquez: Nurse. Let's call it a day.
本:我改变主意了,我愿意把扁桃体割掉.
Ben: I've changed my mind. I'm happy to have my tonsils out.
护士:好了医生,那明天早上再见.
Nurse: Alright, Doctor. See you in the morning.
本:你们割我的什么都可以,割我的阑尾,我求你了.
Ben: Or anything else you want to take out. Take my appendix, please!
玛奎兹医生:明天早点,做手术的人很多.
Dr. Marquez: Get here early, we got a lot of people to cut up!
护士:不能等!
Nurse: Can't wait!
本:不能等!!
Ben: No!
本:妈妈,爸爸,迈克,开萝尔.
Ben: Mom! Dad! Mike! Carol!
杰森:你别讲话.
Jason: Save your voice. Don't try to talk.
本:你们听得见我吗?
Ben: You guys can hear me?
迈克:当然能听见.
Mike: Always.
本:我改变主意,我决定把我的扁桃体割掉.
Ben: I changed my mind. I'm happy to have my tonsils out.
杰森:抱歉,太晚了.
Jason: Uh, sorry. You're too late.
本:哦,不,不,不.
Ben: Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
麦琪:你爸爸的意思是,你不能再割第二次了本.
Maggie: No, honey. What your father means is that you can't take them out again, Ben.
本:你喊我本.
Ben: You called me Ben.
麦琪:是啊.
Maggie: Yea.
杰森:你一生下来就是这样喊你的.
Jason: Well, we've been doing that since you were a kid.
本:今天不是,因为我逃回家,
Ben: Not today, cause see I went home cause I didn't want my tonsils out
因为我害怕把扁桃割掉,
and you guys were there,
你们都在那可看不见我,那有个小混蛋你们都喊他Ben.
but you didn't see me and there was this weeny guy and you called him Ben.
迈克:那小混蛋是你.
Mike: Ben, you're the weeny.
麦琪:你说的准是梦里的事,小南瓜.
Maggie: That must've been some dream, pumpkin.
本:喊我声本.
Ben: Call me Ben.
麦琪:本.
Maggie: Ben.
本:谢谢.
Ben: Thank you.
杰森:你看这都是因为你害怕看刀,所以才会做出这种怪梦,问题出在这儿.
Jason: So your fears about this operations and all those wild dreams you had, well, that's all up here.
开萝尔:他脑子里也就这么点玩意儿.
Carol: That's about the only thing up there.
本:爸爸,妈妈,
Ben: Mom, Dad, Everybody.
哥哥,姐姐我想对你们说,我能够姓西维尔真使我激动.
I just want to say being a Seaver makes me feel really swell!
家人:激动?
Everybody: Swell?
本:这是真的,现在开始我要做一个最最好的孩子,
Ben: I'm serious. From now on,
我要干干净净的,
I'm gonna try to be the best Ben I can be.
不再乱喊乱叫,不再做怪事.
No more pigging out, no more screaming, no more weird stuff.
杰森:不知道他们给他用的哪种麻药.
本:妈妈爸爸我想告诉你们,我为姓西维尔而自豪.你,你,你!
00:22:41,300
Jason: What kind of anesthesia did they give him? Ben: Mom, Dad. I just want to say, I'll be proud to be a Seaver. You! You! You!